dailyshop.com 2013-05-15

# Input Help Topics - Privacy Policy - DailyShop.com

We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site, such as your name, phone number, address, email and any other data or information that would allow someone to personally identify you. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site.

How do we use the information?  
We use customer contact information to fill orders, contact prior purchasers to inform you of your order status, to trace false orders, to remind customers of events through our reminder service(s), and to send service emails, newsletters, and promotional emails from us or third parties. We also use these information to prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft and otherwise protect our customers and our business.

How secure is information about our customers?  
We offer secure web pages to collect certain kinds of user information and we store certain kinds of data in encrypted form. We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. We employ physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of any personally identifiable information.

We do not sell, trade or rent your Personally Identifiable Information collected on our Sites to others. You expressly consent to the sharing of your Personally Identifiable Information with third-parties as described below.

 Service Providers  
We may share information with companies that provide support services to us (such as a printer, e-mail, mobile marketing, or data enhancement provider) or that help us market our products and services. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions.

These companies are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any other purpose.

Legal Requirements  
We may disclose information you provide to us when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law; to enforce or apply applicable terms and conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, our guests or others.

Please note that all the transactions are processed by Dailyshop's fully owned subsidiary SOFTISLAND LLC LIMITED located in Suite 250,162-168 Regent Street, London W1B 5TD. 

Financial institution  
We may disclose personally identifiable information to a financial institution to fulfill your payment.
